[music]
I was a kid looking for love, full of hope inside.
[music and singing] But time was never kind to me.
My heart grew cold as ice. All out of luck.
Thought I was stuck alone for all my life.
But I was proven wrong the moment I looked in your eyes.
It's true.
Until I'm in the grave.
Darling, I love you for a thousand years.
Dear, time is nothing when I'm here with you.
Oh my fears, tears, those memories disappear with you.
[music]
Till I turn to dust.
I'm curious of my death for a thousand years.
[music]
Soon something will bloom like a lotus flower.
The blessed moon will soon be sun and turn to golden hour.
Hours and days lost in your gaze, losing track of time.
Learning how to slow it down. Appreciate our lives.
Just know until I'm in the grave.
Darling, I love you for a thousand years.
Tell me nothing when I'm here with you.
All my fears, tears, those memories that disappear with you.
Till I turn into dust.
[music]
On fire. Let it burn bright.
On the liar.
[music]
I love you for a thousand years.
Dear, time is nothing when I'm here with you.
All my fears, tears, those memories that disappear with you.
Oh my.
[music]
[music] for a thousand years.